Daylan Hoff

Computer Scientist

Contact & Info

Address

Salt Lake City, UT, 84105

Phone

(435) 592-5991

E-mail

daylan.hoff@gmail.com

Website

https://www.daylanhoff.com

Github

https://github.com/DaylanHoff

Skills

C#

.NET & ASP

C++

Java

Java Script

Node JS / Express

Python

Microsoft SQL

MySQL

MongoDB

Current Student at Neumont College of Computer Science working towards a Computer Science Degree. More than 4 years of experience repairing and building computers, and laptops. Able to effectively analyze diagnose problems including driver issues, hardware failure etc.. Extensive knowledge in multiple programming languages such as c#, c++, Java, .Net, and Python. With asic experience with industry networking. Team leader effectively able to communicate with others and take charge of problems.

Work History

2019-01 -2019-04

Customer Support Agent

Netbyte Software, Remote

- Trained new personnel regarding company operations, policies and services.
- Promoted available products and services to customers during service, account management and order calls.
- Removed malware, ransomware and other threats from laptops and desktop systems.
- Troubleshot and diagnosed problems to accurately resolve wide range of technical issues.
- Patched software and installed new versions to eliminate security problems and protect data.

2019-04 -2020-03

Full Stack Developer

Netbyte Software, Remote

- Used Java to create the core application including front and back end development
- Worked heavily with the customer support team to fix bugs, and contributed to 40% reduction of customer complaints
- Utilized JUnit to properly test and validate our software helping reduce a large majority of bugs.
- Used MySQL and other programming languages like Python to help query data bases and gather data.

Education

2018-10 -Current

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science And Programming

Neumont University - Salt Lake City, UT